Guide to the Office of Alumni Relations records, 1848-2005 RG0026
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Alumni house files, 1957-1985; RG0026 Series 3; 10.5 Linear feet
  - San Francisco Alumni, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - San Francisco Alumni, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Regional - San Francisco CA, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - San Francisco, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - San Francisco, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - San Francisco Regional Mtgs. (Past), undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Salt Lake City, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Letter, Ellwood A. Smith to Fred WInfield Weitzel, Inauguration of George D. Culler, President of the Philadelphia College of Art, 04/11/1966; RG0026 Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Photographs of distinguished alumni, 1990-1998; RG0026 Series 4; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of photos and slides of distinguished alumni awards events, campus scenes, and videotapes. The material ranges in date from 1990-98, and were transferred to University Archives in 2004.
- General alumni association files, 1959-2005; RG0026 Series 5; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of general alumni association, files, including governing and executive board lists, governing board by-laws, meeting minutes, distinguished alumni award lists, alumni service awards, alumni trustees, and photos. They range in date from 1959-99, and were transferred to University Archives in 2003.
  - Governing Board lists, 1966-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GAA Committee on the Alumni Program, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Volunteer Service Award list, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Community Service Award list, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni trustees list, 1982-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Service Awards list, 1959-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAA Governing Board and Executive Board meetings, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Special Meeting-topics include Board of Directors rosters, Committee lists, DAAA recipients and alternates, Alumni Service Awards, 09/17/1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photos and C.V.'s of 1999 Distinguished Alumni Award Winners (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Governing Board Members, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    In binder titled Governing Board
  - Governing Board Committees, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Governing Board By-Laws, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1986-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Alumni Association Service Awards, 1988-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Trustees, 1989-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Relations Guidelines, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Constitution, GAA Articles of Associaton and By-Laws, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Constitution of the GAA, 1925 Outline (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Constitutions (Constituent Organizations), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - By-Laws of GAA, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Articles and By-Laws of the GAA, 1960-1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board, 1984-1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Constitution Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - By-Laws Amendment -- 1996, 10/17/1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Attendance -- GWAA Board of Directors Meetings, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - By-Laws -- Original -- Revision February 6, 2002, 02/06/2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - GWAA By-Laws Amendments Document 2003, John R. Manning (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - GWAA Nominating Committee, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - GWAA Board Applications, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Outreach and Activities, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - General Alumni Association Citation, Dr. Irene I-Lien Hsu (Siu), 06/03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Alumni association board of directors files, 1994-1999; RG0026 Series 6; 4 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of correspondence and memos relating to alumni association board of directors, governing board, executive committee meetings, distinguished alumni achievement awards, and service awards. The materials range in date from 1994-99, and were transferred to University Archives in 2002.
  - GWAA Board of Directors Meeting, 04/30/1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GWAA Board of Directors Meeting, 01/29/1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, 10/17/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, 06/12/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Biennial meeting
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, 05/01/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, 01/31/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - GAA Governing Board Election, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - GAA Governing Board Election, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, 10/24/1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, 05/03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - GAA Governing Board Meeting, 02/01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 04/22/1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 01/15/1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 12/05/1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    RE: Mission statement of the university
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 11/05/1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    GAA President; Allesica Morrison, esq.; campaign leadership transition
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 10/22/1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 10/08/1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 04/13/1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 01/23/1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 10/17/1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 04/25/1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 01/24/1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    General information and photographs
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Nominations, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    General information
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award recipients, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Photographs
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Nominations, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Monumental Celebration, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Nominations, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Packet, 09/19/1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Packet, 09/14/1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Packet, 09/19/1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Packet, 09/11/1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 04/21/1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 01/20/1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - GAA Executive Committee Meeting, 10/14/1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - GAA Board of Directors Meeting, 04/29/1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - GAA Board of Directors Meeting, 01/28/1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - GAA Board of Directors Meeting, 10/23/1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - GAA Alumni Trustee, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Special meeting regarding Gary Granoff
  - GAA Alumni Trustee, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GAA Alumni Trustee, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - GAA Alumni Trustee, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Trustee Nomination Packet, 06/02/1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Trustee Nomination Packet, 12/16/1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - GAA Governing Board, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - GAA Election, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - GAA Alumni Trustee Recommendations Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - GAA Distinguished Alumni Achievement Awards Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - GAA By-laws Committe, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - GAA Reunion Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - GAA Alumni Recognition Awards, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - GAA Alumni Recognition Awards, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - GAA Alumni Recognition Awards, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- T-shirt, 2001; RG0026 Series 7; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of a t-shirt from alumni weekend, and dates from 2001. It was transferred to University Archives in 2001.
  Formerly ACC#1014.
- Binders, 1970-1989; RG0026 Series 8; 3 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of six binders of invitations, schedules, programs, etc., of various alumni events. They range in date from 1970-89, and material was added to the University Archives collections from a backlog in 2001.
- Contact sheets and negatives, 1988; RG0026 Series 9; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of alumni reunion contact sheets and negatives. They date from 1988 and were transferred to University Archives in 1995.
- Photos from old events, 1965-1992; RG0026 Series 10; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series consists of photos from alumni relations events, Lloyd Elliott, Elmer Kayser, alumni reunion weekends, campus buildings, distinguished alumni awards dinners, football reception, Jack Morton alumni lounge, homecoming, etc.. They range in date from 1965-1992, and were added to the University Archives collections from a backlog in 2000.
  - Reunion negotiations [1/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
    2 copies
  - Reunion negotiations [2/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
  - Reunion negotiations [3/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - Reunion negotiations [4/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.4)
  - Reunion negotiations [5/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - Reunion negotiations [6/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.6)
  - Reunion negotiations [7/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.7)
  - Reunion negotiations [8/8], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.8)
  - Open air reception [1/2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.9)
  - Open air reception [2/2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Unidentified individual [1/2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.11)
  - Unidentified individual [2/2], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1.12)
  - President Elliot chatting with two others [1/2], 08/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1.13)
  - President Elliot chatting with two others [2/2], 08/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1.14)
  - B.L. Cruch, 08/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1.15)
  - Dinner Hall Scene, 08/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1.16)
  - Groups chatting, 08/1987 (Box 1, Folder 1.17)
  - Groups chatting after meal [1/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.18)
  - Groups chatting after meal [2/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.19)
  - Groups chatting after meal [3/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
  - Groups chatting after meal [4/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.21)
  - Groups chatting after meal [5/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.22)
  - Groups chatting after meal [6/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.23)
  - Groups chatting after meal [7/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.24)
  - Groups chatting after meal [8/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.25)
  - Groups chatting after meal [9/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.26)
  - Groups chatting after meal [10/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.27)
  - Groups chatting after meal [11/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.28)
  - Groups chatting after meal [12/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.29)
  - Groups chatting after meal [13/13], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - An unidentified statue [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.31)
  - An unidentified statue [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.32)
  - Group chatting after meal [1/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.33)
  - Group chatting after meal [2/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.34)
  - Group chatting after meal [3/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.35)
  - Group chatting after meal [4/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.36)
  - Group chatting after meal [5/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.37)
  - Group chatting after meal [6/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.38)
  - Group chatting after meal [7/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.39)
  - Group chatting after meal [8/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.4)
  - Group chatting after meal [9/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.41)
  - Group chatting after meal [10/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.42)
  - Group chatting after meal [11/11], undated (Box 1, Folder 1.43)
  - Mr & Mrs. Stern cuttin the Rug, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.44)
  - Mrs. Bernice Stern with husband, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.45)
  - Charles and Phyllis Pickens, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.46)
  - Mr & Mrs Everett Woodward, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.47)
  - Harvey C & Jean Wright/Col, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.48)
  - Mrs. Margaret Mills Ball/Col and her husband, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.49)
  - Fifty year dinner at Wyndan Bristal, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.5)
  - Woodwards (left) & Pickens, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.51)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Armand Gordon, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.52)
  - Members dancing, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.53)
  - Reunion Negotiations, Negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.54)
    2 sleeves
  - Woodson, Michael A. Lewis, 07/1980 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - Alumni Records Office, Don Conrad, 07/1980 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - Alumni Records Office, Sondra Woodson on terminal & printer, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - Alumni Records Office, Michael Lewis, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - Alumni Records Office, Sondra Woodson, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - Alumni in News, Tidal McCoy, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - Alumni in News, Richard de Camora, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Alumni in News, B/G Robert E. Kelly, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Alumni in News, Conrad, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
  - Alumni in News, William Colhan, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
  - Alumni in News, Thomas F. Gizicki, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.6)
  - Alumni in News, Paul Corcoran, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.7)
  - Alumni in News, Henry Cisneros, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.8)
  - Alumni in News, John Rogers, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.9)
  - Alumni Fun Day, Different Functions [1/7], 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - Alumni Fun Day, Different Functions [2/7], 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Alumni Fun Day, Different Functions [3/7], 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.3)
  - Alumni Fun Day, Different Functions [4/7], 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.4)
  - Alumni Fun Day, Different Functions [5/7], 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.5)
  - Alumni Fun Day, Different Functions [6/7], 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.6)
  - Alumni Fun Day, Different Functions [7/7], 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.7)
  - Florida Alumni, Dining Scene, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - Florida Alumni,Ellwood Smith, Dr. Symon Alpert, Edwina Avery, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - Florida, Alumni, Different Scenes [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 5.3)
  - Florida, Alumni, Different Scenes [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 5.4)
  - Alumni Functions, GW Alumni & friends in Lybia, 01/1962 (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
  - Alumni Functions, Alumni gathering after GW Temple game - Mrs. Mary Kelly, Mrs. Stanley Sommer, Mr. Wynn Weitzel, Mrs. Weitzel, Mrs. Stanley Sommers, 09/18/1965 (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - Alumni Functions Susan Fisher, Ted Linder, Bruce Innes at the Alumni Leader's Conference, 10/02/1965 (Box 1, Folder 6.3)
  - Alumni Functions, Skip Gnehm, Ted Lindner, Pat Dryden at the Alumni Leader's Conference held at Airlie House, Warrenton, Virginia, 10/02/1965 (Box 1, Folder 6.4)
  - Alumni Functions, Dining scene, Philadelphia, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.5)
  - Alumni Functions, Reception at Strong Hall Lounge, 03/10/1982 (Box 1, Folder 6.6)
  - Exhibit Photos, G.W. students who became prominent people [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - Exhibit Photos, G.W. students who became prominent people [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
  - Alumni Dinner, University Center [1/2], 04/18/1970 (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
  - Alumni Dinner, University Center [2/2], 04/18/1970 (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
  - Alumni Crew, Andy Findlay, BA '61, 10/31/1981 (Box 1, Folder 9.1)
  - Alumni Crew, Alumni Crew Winners 25th Reunion, 10/31/1981 (Box 1, Folder 9.2)
  - Alumni Crew, 25th Crew Reunion Cake, 10/31/1981 (Box 1, Folder 9.3)
  - Alumni Collections, Michael L. Coats, GW Alumnus pilot on Discovery, 07/24/1980 (Box 1, Folder 10.1)
  - Alumni Collections, Graduate School Reception for graduate students and Alumni office extenship party, 12/06/1983 (Box 1, Folder 10.2)
  - Alumni Collections, Leggette Room Pictures, 10/26/1974 (Box 1, Folder 10.3)
  - Alumni Collections, Opening at Dimock Gallery, 11/07/1974 (Box 1, Folder 10.4)
  - Alumni Collections, Alumni Officers, Bud Wareham, Joan Regnell, Dee Parkinson, Cook, Ellwood Smith, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10.5)
  - Alumni Collections, Alumni in Kiev, undated (Box 1, Folder 10.6)
  - Alumni Collections, Jessica Josephson J.D., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10.7)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust Co., N.Y., 08/1976 (Box 1, Folder 10.8)
  - Alumni Collections, Edmund David Osinki Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 10.9)
  - Alumni Collections, Roger H. Rageot, undated (Box 1, Folder 10.1)
  - Alumni Collections, Charles A. Barton, undated (Box 1, Folder 10.11)
  - Alumni Collections, Timothy D. Mead [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 10.12)
  - Alumni Collections, Timothy D. Mead [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 10.13)
  - Alumni Collections, Alumni Relations Office's Poster, undated (Box 1, Folder 10.14)
  - Alumni Awards Reception, U.S. Botanical Garden [1/2], 05/10/1981 (Box 1, Folder 11.1)
  - Alumni Awards Reception, U.S. Botanical Garden [2/2], 05/10/1981 (Box 1, Folder 11.2)
  - Alumni Awards Reception, 06/08/1980 (Box 1, Folder 12.1)
  - Alumni Awards Reception, Porter William with his Alumni Service Award, Nancy Dudsey, Mr. & Mrs. Porter, William Smith, Children Billay and Carolin Porter, 06/08/1980 (Box 1, Folder 12.2)
  - Alumni Awards Reception, 06/03/1979 (Box 1, Folder 13.1)
  - Alumni Awards Reception, Rupert Woodward's Retirement Recep., 06/01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 13.2)
  - Alumni Service Awards Ceremony [1/2], 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14.1)
  - Alumni Service Awards Ceremony [2/2], 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14.2)
  - Commencement, 06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 14.3)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [1/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.1)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [2/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.2)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [3/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.3)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [4/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.4)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [5/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.5)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [6/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.6)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [7/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.7)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [8/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.8)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [9/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.9)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [10/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.1)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [11/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.11)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [12/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.12)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [13/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.13)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [14/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.14)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [15/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.15)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [16/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.16)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [17/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.17)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [18/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.18)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [19/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.19)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [20/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.2)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Group photo [21/21], 06/1987 (Box 1, Folder 15.21)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [1/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.1)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [2/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.2)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [3/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.3)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [4/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.4)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [5/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.5)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [6/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.6)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [7/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.7)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [8/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.8)
  - Reunion, Groups attending a function [9/9], undated (Box 1, Folder 16.9)
  - Reunion, Men's basketball game, undated (Box 1, Folder 16.1)
  - Homecoming, Dinner Dance [1/4], 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.1)
  - Homecoming, Dinner Dance [2/4], 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.2)
  - Homecoming, Dinner Dance [3/4], 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.3)
  - Homecoming, Dinner Dance [4/4], 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.4)
  - Homecoming, Students with balloons, 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.5)
  - Homecoming, Students at entrance of Alumni House, 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.6)
  - Homecoming, Two members, 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.7)
  - Homecoming, Members chatting [1/3], 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.8)
  - Homecoming, Members chatting [2/3], 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.9)
  - Homecoming, Members chatting [3/3], 02/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 17.1)
  - Colonial Ambassadors [1/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 18.1)
  - Colonial Ambassadors [2/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 18.2)
  - Colonial Ambassadors [3/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 18.3)
  - Colonial Ambassadors [4/4], undated (Box 1, Folder 18.4)
  - Capitol Hill Photo [1/2], 09/1991 (Box 1, Folder 19.1)
  - Capitol Hill Photo [2/2], 09/1991 (Box 1, Folder 19.2)
  - Capitol HIll Reception [1/4], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20.1)
  - Capitol HIll Reception [2/4], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20.2)
  - Capitol HIll Reception [3/4], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20.3)
  - Capitol HIll Reception [4/4], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20.4)
  - Campus Buildings, National Law Center Lerner Hall, S.W.corner of H & 20th, undated (Box 1, Folder 21.1)
  - Campus buildings, G Street Firehouse (between 21st and 22nd), undated (Box 1, Folder 21.2)
  - Campus Buildings, Woodhall House Corner (S.E) of G & 21st, undated (Box 1, Folder 21.3)
  - ARC Meeting [1/2], 10/12/1989 (Box 1, Folder 22.1)
  - ARC Meeting [2/2], 10/12/1989 (Box 1, Folder 22.2)
  - Alumni Course Audit Registration [1/2], 06/1991 (Box 1, Folder 23.1)
  - Alumni Course Audit Registration [2/2], 06/1991 (Box 1, Folder 23.2)
  - Alumni Service Awards, American Inst. of Architects [1/3], 06/01/1990 (Box 1, Folder 24.1)
  - Alumni Service Awards, American Inst. of Architects [2/3], 06/01/1990 (Box 1, Folder 24.2)
  - Alumni Service Awards, American Inst. of Architects [3/3], 06/01/1990 (Box 1, Folder 24.3)
  - Campus Buildings, undated (Box 1, Folder 25.1)
  - Reunion 1991, Alumni Reunion Weekend, 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.1)
  - Reunion 1991, Alumni Reunion 1941 Lecture, 04/12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.2)
  - Reunion 1991, Carnival on the Quad, Smith Center, 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.3)
  - Reunion 1991, Class of 1981 Reunion, Brick Skellor, 04/12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.4)
  - Reunion 1991, undated (Box 1, Folder 26.5)
  - Reunion 1991, Reunion Gala [1/2], 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.6)
  - Reunion 1991, Reunion Gala [2/2], 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.7)
  - Reunion 1991, 50 Yr. Reunion Lunch, 25 Yr. party, Elliott Rm, 04/12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.8)
  - Reunion 1991, (1) Class of 1971 Party (2) '66 Party, 04/12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.9)
  - Reunion 1991, Carnival Class of 1986 Reunion, Gala, undated (Box 1, Folder 26.1)
  - Reunion 1991, President's Brunch for 1941 [1/2], 04/14/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.11)
  - Reunion 1991, President's Brunch for 1941 [2/2], 04/14/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.12)
  - Reunion 1991, Carnival on the Quad, 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.13)
  - Reunion 1991, President's Brunch for 1941, 04/14/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.14)
  - Reunion 1991, Reunion Gala, President's Brunch, 04/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.15)
  - Reunion 1991, Carnival on the Quad, Smith Center [1/3], 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.16)
  - Reunion 1991, Carnival on the Quad, Smith Center [2/3], 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.17)